<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Base Project</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_header_title" translatable="false">LEGO®</string>

    <!-- Translatable resources -->
    <string name="grid" translation_description="Common Filter">Switch between grid and list</string>
    <string name="legothemes_title">Browse Themes</string>
    <string name="legosets_title">Browse All Sets</string>
    <string name="legoset_details_title">Set details</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_header_content_description">Navigation drawer header logo</string>
    <string name="menu_item_share" translation_description="The label for the Share menu item">Share</string>
    <string name="number_of_parts">Number of parts: %d</string>
    <string name="year">Year: %d</string>
<!--    <string name="share_lego_set">Check out %s Lego set : %s</string>-->

    <!-- Accessibility -->
    <string name="a11y_legoset_item_image">Picture of Lego Set</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="app_logo">App Logo</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="password_hint">●●●●●●●●●●●●</string>
    <string name="email_example">username@example.com</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="image">IMG</string>
    <string name="long_text">The code is below. When fragment loads, it covers the toolbar and my floating action bar. How can I handle this? I want the toolbar to show. It seems there is some overlapping in coordinatorlayout. I have checked out different problems like this. None seems to answer my question   The code is below. When fragment loads, it covers the toolbar and my floating action bar. How can I handle this? I want the toolbar to show. It seems there is some overlapping in coordinatorlayout. I have checked out different problems like this. None seems to answer my question   The code is below. When fragment loads, it covers the toolbar and my floating action bar. How can I handle this? I want the toolbar to show. It seems there is some overlapping in coordinatorlayout. I have checked out different problems like this. None seems to answer my question   The code is below. When fragment loads, it covers the toolbar and my floating action bar. How can I handle this? I want the toolbar to show. It seems there is some overlapping in coordinatorlayout. I have checked out different problems like this. None seems to answer my question</string>

    <string name="userId">User id</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="company">Company</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="browse_by_category">Browse by category</string>
    <string name="posts">User Posts</string>


</resources>
